Guide to the Multicultural Student Services Center records, 1969-2016 RG0056
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Multicultural Student Services Center, 1969-1993; 1980-1993; RG0056 Series 1
  - Summer Advance Registration Program (SARP) and HI/SCIP Letters, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Staff Travel, May 31, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Entering Educational Opportunity Program Student Data (Compiled), 1968-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Entering Educational Opportunity Program Student Data (Raw), 1969-1973; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Student Update Form (Blank), 1979; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Student Update Form (Blank), 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Newspapers: Gay Community News, 1977; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Series 1 Box 14 was transferred by Timothy Kaine in 2019. Kaine is the Associate Director, Inclusion Initiatives at GW and Director of the Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Resource Center.
  - Newspapers: Gay Sunshine and Fag Rag, 1973-1974; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - Newspapers, 1970-1980; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - Boston Institute for Gay Studies material, 1981-1983; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Boston Institute for Gay Studies binder, 1983; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    Documents should be checked for private information.
    Series 1 Box 15 was transferred by Timothy Kaine in 2019. Kaine is the Associate Director, Inclusion Initiatives at GW and Director of the Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Resource Center.
  - Abstracts of articles on homosexuality, 1976; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Billings to/ Receipts from the Federal Government, July 7, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 99)
- Brochures, RG0056 Series 2; 0.25 Linear feet
  This series contains brochures about the Multicultural Student Services Center and the Diversity Program Clearinghouse.
  - Multicultural Student Services Center (Box 1, Folder 1)
- GW memorial materials related to Pulse nightclub shooting, 2016; RG0056 Series 3; 2.25 Linear Feet 1 oversize folder, 1 slim document box
  This series contains posters and slips of paper inscribed by GW faculty, staff and students in remembrance and celebration of the GLBT and Latinx community members who died in the Pulse Orlando nightclub shooting, including one poster that was defaced while on display
  - Posters and slips of paper inscribed by GW faculty, staff and students (Folder 1)
  - One "GW Celebrates PRIDE" tank top and 11 buttons with pride, ally and preferred pronoun statements, 2016; Series 3 Box 2 (Box 1)